Guide to the Jason Altmire Congressional Papers, 2006-2012 AIS.2013.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Moving Image Files, 2007-2013; XIII.
  - C-SPAN Coverage, 2007-2013; 1.
    - Altmire in Speaker's Chair Appearances, 2007-2008 (Folder 140)
    - Committee Hearings, 2007-2012 (Folder 141)
  - Media Appearances, 2007-2013; 2.
    This subseries contains all appearances of the Congressman on local and national news programs during his tenure. These videos include interviews, television spots, and press mentions. The files highlight several of his career highs: his role as a Democratic Superdelegate during the 2008 presidential election, his involvement in the Haiti airlift in January 2010, and his role in the 2010 Affordable Care Act debate. The files are arranged chronologically. See Series X, Subseries 1 for the corresponding monthly logs of these interviews.
    - 2007 (Folder 142)
    - 2008 (Folder 143)
    - 2009 (Folder 144)
    - 2010 (Folder 145)
    - 2011 (Folder 146)
    - 2012 (Folder 147)
    - 2013 (Folder 148)
    - Interview Transcripts, 2010 (Folder 149)
  - Various Recordings and Appearances, 2007-2012; 3.
    This subseries contains recorded appearances of the Congressman at various events in his district and around the country, as well as official and unofficial messages addressing local and national issues. The files are arranged alphabetically.
    - Commercials, 2008, 2011 (Folder 150)
    - Constituent Issues Support Videos, 2006-2008, 2011 (Folder 151)
    - D.C. and Out of District Event Videos, 2009-2012 (Folder 152)
    - District Event Videos, 2007-2011 (Folder 153)
    - Keynote Addresses, 2009-2011 (Folder 154)
    - Patriocracy Segment, 2011 (Folder 155)
    - Protest Videos, 2010 (Folder 156)
    - Public Service Announcements, 2007, 2011 (Folder 157)
- Photographic Files, 2006-2012; XIV.
  This series contains photographs of the Congressman's campaign, legislative activities, district events, D.C. events, international travel, administrative photographs, and photographs with VIPs. The series is arranged into subseries alphabetically by subject.
  - Administrative and Congressional Photographs, 2006-2013; 1.
    This subseries contains photographs of the Congressman's offices, staff, and speeches on the House floor. The files are arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - Aliquippa Office, 2012 (Folder 158)
    - D.C. Office, 2012 (Folder 159)
    - Floor Speech Stills, 2007, 2010-2012 (Folder 160)
    - Natrona Heights Office, 2012 (Folder 161)
    - Official Headshots, 2006-2009 (Folder 162)
    - Staff and Interns, 2008-2013 (Folder 163)
  - Campaign Photographs, 2006-2012; 2.
    This subseries contains photographs taken during the Congressman's three election campaigns. These include photographs of campaign events, rallies, canvassing by the Congressman and his volunteers, speaking events, and official Citizens for Altmire photo opportunities. The files are arranged chronologically.
    - 2006 (Folder 164)
    - 2007 (Folder 165)
    - 2008 (Folder 166)
    - 2009 (Folder 167)
    - 2010 (Folder 168)
    - 2011 (Folder 169)
    - 2012 (Folder 170)
  - Congressional Delegation Photographs, 2007-2012; 3.
    This subseries contains photographs taken by the Congressman or members of his delegation on each of his overseas trips. The photographs are arranged chronologically.
    - CODEL to Iraq, August 2007 (Folder 171)
    - CODEL to China/South Korea, July 2012 (Folder 172)
    - CODEL to Georgia/Slovakia, July 2012 (Folder 173)
  - D.C. and Out of District Events, 2007-2012; 4.
    This subseries contains photographs taken of the Congressman at various events in the District of Columbia and around the country during his tenure. These include official House events, rallies, dinners, balls, and roundtable discussions. The files are arranged chronologically.
    - 2007 (Folder 174)
    - 2008 (Folder 175)
    - 2009 (Folder 176)
    - 2010 (Folder 177)
    - 2011 (Folder 178)
    - 2012 (Folder 179)
  - District Events, 2007-2012; 5.
    This subseries contains photographs taken of the Congressman at various events within the PA-04 district tenure. These include rallies, speaking engagements, small business visits, senior citizen outreach, roundtables, town halls, and community events. The files are arranged chronologically.
    - 2007 (Folder 180)
    - 2008 (Folder 181)
    - 2009 (Folder 182)
    - 2010 (Folder 183)
    - 2011 (Folder 184)
    - 2012 (Folder 185)
  - VIP Photographs, 2006-2012; 6.
    This subseries contains photographs of the Congressman with various celebrities, business magnates, politicians, and presidents. The files are arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - Business Leaders, 2010-2012 (Folder 186)
    - Foreign Leaders, 2007, 2011-2012 (Folder 187)
    - Movie and Television Celebrities, 2007-2012 (Folder 188)
    - Musicians, 2007-2012 (Folder 189)
    - Politicians, 2006-2012 (Folder 190)
    - Presidents, 2007-2012 (Folder 191)
    - Sports Figures, 2009-2012 (Folder 192)
- Recorded Audio and Sound Files, 2006-2013; XV.
  This series contains audio recordings of the Congressman speaking. These primarily consist of radio interviews, telephone town halls, and various other recordings.
  - Radio Interviews, 2006-2013; 1.
    This subseries contains recordings of interviews the Congressman gave to various radio stations within his district and D.C. The files are arranged chronologically. See Series X, Subseries 1 for the monthly logs of these interviews.
    - 2006 (Folder 193)
    - 2007 (Folder 194)
    - 2008 (Folder 195)
    - 2009 (Folder 196)
    - 2010 (Folder 197)
    - 2011 (Folder 198)
    - 2012 (Folder 199)
  - Various Recordings, 2008-2012; 2.
    This subseries contains recorded meetings the Congressman held with his constituents and other parties during his tenure. These recordings consist of telephone town halls, roundtable discussions, press conferences, and saved voicemail messages.
    - 2008 (Folder 200)
    - 2009 (Folder 201)
    - 2011 (Folder 202)
    - 2012 (Folder 203)
- "Citizens for Altmire" Campaign Files, 2006-2012; XVI.
  This series contains polling data related to Congressman Altmire's four election campaigns. The files include baseline surveys, constituent demographic tables, third-party analyses of the data, and copies of verbatim polling responses. The series is arranged chronologically. Please see Series XIV, Subseries 2 for photographs related to campaign events.
  - 2006 (Folder 204)
  - 2008 (Folder 205)
  - 2009 (Folder 206)
  - 2010 (Folder 207)
  - 2012 (Folder 208)